delvenetworks.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Limelight Networks

Welcome to the Limelight Networks, Inc. (“Limelight”) web site ([www.limelight.com](http://www.limelight.com/) the “Site”) and Limelight services platform (the “Limelight Platform”), operated and produced by Limelight. Limelight values the privacy of the users, subscribers, publishers, members, and others who visit and use the Limelight Platform (collectively or individually, “you” or “Users”).

This privacy policy covers the web site [www.limelight.com](http://www.limelight.com/), as well as the Limelight Platform. By using the Site or Limelight Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or Limelight Platform.

This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with the Limelight Acceptable Use Policy. Your use of the Site and Limelight Platform and any personally identifiable information you provide are subject at all times to this Privacy Policy and the Acceptable Use Policy. 

Limelight Networks, Inc. complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Limelight Networks, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Limelight Networks, Inc.’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

TABLE OF CONTENTS

  1. The Information Limelight Collects
  2. The Way Limelight Uses Information
  3. When Limelight Discloses Information
  4. Your Choices
  5. Data Security
  6. Children's Privacy
  7. International Visitors
  8. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy
  9. Effective Date, Date Last Modified
  10. Unsolicited E-mails
  11. Limelight Contact Information

## 1\. The Information Limelight Collects:

User-provided Information: You may provide to Limelight what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, enter contests or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the Site and Limelight Platform. You may also provide to Limelight demographic information; information related to your web site such as the name, description and primary language of the site; and company name, telephone number, e-mail address, mailing address, and personal contacts within your company.

The Limelight Platform enables you to provide us with certain data in order to be maintained and processed through our network and services ("Customer Data"). We have no control over the data that is submitted to us through our platform. The scope of our services and the data provided to us for processing is subject to the contractual agreements we enter into with our customers.

Limelight also provides an area for people looking for a job at Limelight Networks. In applying for a job or asking for information about a job we may require personally identifiable information from you such as your address or e-mail address.

We will retain the information you provide us and the data we process on behalf of our clients for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide our services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at websupport@llnw.com. We will retain and use the information we receive from you and or your end users as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

"Cookies and Other Technologies" Information: When you access the Site or the Limelight Platform, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Limelight may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site or the Limelight Platform. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Our cookies are linked to personally identifiable information. 

Our web pages, on both the Site and the Limelight Platform, contain electronic image requests (called a "single-pixel gif" or "web beacon" request) that allow us to count page views and to access cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically 1-by-1 pixel files, but their presence can usually be seen within a browser by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." We also include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. Limelight web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personally identifiable information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile anonymous information about web site usage. 

Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers, analytics providers) use cookies and web beacons on our Site and the Limelight Platform (collectively referred to as "tracking technologies). We have no access to or control over these tracking technologies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Limelight only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties. 

"Flash Cookies" Defined: Flash cookies are similar to cookies described above, and are created when you use your video player. Flash cookies are stored in your video player's cache memory. Flash cookies may or may not be removed the same way that cookies are removed. Please review your video player's "Help", "Tools" and or "Options" files to learn more about the proper way to modify your Flash cookie settings. Our Flash cookies are linked to personal information. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use Flash cookies and other tracking technologies on our site. We have no access to or control over these Flash cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of Flash cookies by Limelight only and does not cover the use of Flash cookies by any advertisers.

More information about Flash cookies is available on the Adobe website: <http://www.adobe.com/special/products/flashplayer/security/index.html>

"Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the Limelight Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, JavaScript enablement, the content and pages that you access on the Site or the Limelight Platform, and the dates and times that you visit, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages. 

## 2\. The Way Limelight Uses Information:

Limelight uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Site and the Limelight Platform, to allow us to charge and invoice you, as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. 

We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Site or Limelight Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Site or the Limelight Platform. 

Customer Data will be used in compliance with our contractual obligations and only as necessary to provide our services.

If you opt in to receive promotional communications or newsletters from us, you will be able to opt out of receiving these by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in the promotional email or newsletter received from us. Limelight uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Customers, to improve the way the Site and the Limelight Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

Limelight may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies and Other Technologies" information to: (a) automatically update the Limelight application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Site or the Limelight Platform; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. 

Our advertising partners help us to display and manage advertising on other web sites. To do this, they collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other web sites. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of displaying ads that may be relevant to your interests, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Our analytics partners help us in understanding how you interact with our Site and services platform.

Information submitted to Limelight as part of applications for employment or for partner candidates is used by Limelight to evaluate your qualifications for the positions sought.Limelight also supplements personally identifiable information collected with information from marketing databases.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 

Your friend may contact us at unsubscribe@llnw.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

## 3\. When Limelight Discloses Information:

Limelight does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Site or Limelight Platform becomes publicly available and may be read, collected and used by others without restriction. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

We also have testimonials on our site. Any user that has provided a testimonial on our site allows us to post their testimonial and personally identifiable information on the site. 

We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; job board services, fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Limelight in improving the Site or the Limelight Platform and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. 

Limelight may share aggregate statistical information gathered from you and other Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a web site or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out registration forms. We share such information only on an aggregate and anonymous basis. 

Limelight may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena warrant, or legal process in the manner required by the requesting entity. 

In the event that Limelight is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

Limelight also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Limelight from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Site and the Limelight Platform; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Limelight, our Users, or others. 

## 4\. Your Choices and Access:

You may, of course, decline to share your personally identifiable information with Limelight, in which case Limelight will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Site or the Limelight Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your User information and preferences, or request the removal of your information from publicly available areas by sending us a request at: websupport@llnw.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. We will respond to your access request within 30 days. 

You do not need to set up a user id and password to use our web sites because we do not require you to establish your identity when you visit our Site. However, if you have subscribed for some of our services or are a customer seeking access to your account information, you will have to provide passwords. We recommend you do not divulge your password to anyone. Limelight will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES.

If you are an account holder, you can update personally identifiable information after logging into your account, under "My Settings", "Edit My Profile". You can update your name, email, address and phone number in this section. 

## 5\. Our Commitment to Data Security:

Limelight uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personally identifiable information, including the use of SSL encryption. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Limelight, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Limelight makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Limelight learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Limelight may post a notice on the Site or the Limelight Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at: websupport@llnw.com. 

## 6\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:

WE DO NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION OF CHILDREN UNDER 13. 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Limelight does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Limelight learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Limelight Platform, then Limelight will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the Limelight Platform, then please contact Limelight at websupport@llnw.com to have that child's information deleted. 

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your childrens' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While Limelight does not endorse these resources, we provide information about them as a public service to our community. 

  * "OnGuard Online," maintained by the Federal Trade Commission
  * WiredSafety
  * Netsmartz.org
  * The Child Safety Network
  * Control Kids
  * Cyber Sitter
  * Net Nanny

## 7\. International Visitors:

For Users visiting the Site or the Limelight Platform from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Site or the Limelight Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by Limelight and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because Limelight operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the Site or the Limelight Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries. 

## 8\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy:

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that personally identifiable information. Your continued use of the Limelight Platform constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personally identifiable information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage) and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information prior to the changes taking effect. 

## 9\. Effective Date, Date Last Modified:

Privacy Policy effective as of April 6, 2015. 

## 10\. Other Information:

Limelight does not send unsolicited e-mails to non-public addresses or to anyone who has asked us not to contact him or her. Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have subscribed to them. To stop receiving e-mails or newsletters from Limelight, either click on an unsubscribe link on the e-mail or newsletter itself or send a request to be unsubscribed to websupport@llnw.com. 

Our Site include links to other web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Limelight Networks, Inc. If you submit personally identifiable information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any web site you visit.

Our Site include social media features, such as the Facebook. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## 11\. Limelight Contact Information:

Please contact Limelight with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personally identifiable information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: Limelight Networks, 222 South Mill Avenue, Suite 800, Tempe, AZ 85281, (602) 850-5000 or by email at: websupport@llnw.com. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.
